bonus weekend video since I missed two
last week
today I'm going to talk about feeling of
inadequacy I am realizing all the places
where I feel that way and instead of
trying to become better in those areas
I'm just trying to accept myself for
exactly where I'm at and also just
seeing the effects that's had on my life
Trump getting into office which I
realize is old news but he has the
opposite of whatever I have like he
thinks he is so he's the best at
everything I mean that's his ego and he
clearly is not he's not even good at
Bizness which is the one thing he should
be good at he's clear bankruptcy how
many times which I realized was maybe
the point but whereas it's not where you
actually are that you're judged on it's
based on where you think you are and all
the areas of my life that I
overcompensate in because I feel like
I'm not as good in them one of the it's
not even the greatest example but one of
the ones that stands out of my my memory
is going to an acquaintance's wedding
and yours in years ago with my ex and
discussing like how much we should put
in the card for money and I put in a few
hundred dollars and at no point have I
been rich so that was a lot of money but
I thought that was like what that's what
people were supposed to do and I got
this like beautiful thank-you card they
divorced within a year but um that I
don't feel good about having given that
money because I felt like I had to like
I was obligated to give it whereas if I
had put in fifty bucks which would have
been way more reasonable I wouldn't even
be thinking about it now but it's the
idea that I felt like I wasn't someone
who gives a good gifts and I wasn't so
therefore I had to overcompensate and I
wasn't in the moment I'm like oh well
give more than everyone else I was it
was the opposite I felt like everyone
gave that amount like I didn't know how
much people gave for a birthday present
you spent like 20 40 bucks so for a
wedding President should be you know
like fifty hundred and there was two of
us so like at least two hundred and for
like a best friend
anyway but that feeling it's not how
much I gave it was that feeling of
feeling inadequate and so
overcompensating and I feel like I do
that in a lot of ways I feel like I am
low-energy so I try to like when I'm
contributing I try to kind of push
through that and give too much and yeah
and that in accepting where I'm at and
also I don't know whether it's better to
actually know where you are on the curve
like to know whether you are better than
average or worse than average or your
average whether it's the need to
actually know that's the problem or
whether it's then not knowing because
their current areas of my life I would
like to know where I fall on the
spectrum like where on the normal curve
am I and I don't know why that would be
helpful but like I feel when I'm in a
group of people and we're all doing work
together especially over the long term
that I don't give enough I'm not one of
the people who is a type-a personality I
don't when those things like give a busy
person if you want something done give
it to a busy person on the opposite I'm
not a busy person so I definitely don't
like needing to run like for errands for
the week overwhelms me and so figuring
out where I am on that I guess that's
another one so if someone comes over to
my house I feel the need to clean it as
I think most people do which ends up
overcompensate and I don't know we're
complicated it's not like I'm cleaning
everything but then I go over to someone
I feel like like if someone was to walk
into my house when it's its normal way
that it is that I'm beyond messy I'm
like a super messy person someone would
like condemn my house and it's nowhere
near that bad like it's stacks of paper
that eventually get put away I'm not a
hoarder I am and walking into other
people's houses that didn't have time to
prep right like my kid walks into
someone's house people don't clean up
for children so then I have to go over
and get her and seeing people as how's
me like oh we all have young kids we all
live like this I
like it's like it's not me being an odd
equipment it's the feeling of being like
I'm not measuring of that like I look
around at the people who look beautiful
all day every day and are decked out in
in amazing fashion and I'm like oh I
don't I don't compete with that
I don't measure up but I don't look at
all the all the you know 80% of the
population or maybe it's 60% of the
population who are out in the sweatpants
and t-shirts like I am like it's like
you know I'm not part of the like lowest
5% I'm just there I'm just you know
average and that's fine and so this
feeling of inadequacy of wear and then
one of the other instances which bugs me
is being female that I'm expected to do
more of the domestic work even when I
don't have a partner so when I'm in a
group of people of two genders really in
this case it doesn't happen so often in
multi gender groups because they've
dealt with a lot of their gender
but women get up and start cleaning and
the men sit around and chat and it's
like an automatic like I'm like I'm
sorry was that supposed to come with my
extra x-chromosome was I supposed to
really want to clean and get up and like
do the dishes because I put in more of
an effort than the men do but less than
the most of the women and so I feel
inadequate as a woman and that people
are not as a woman and like not my
womanliness but like just that I'm not
contributing enough that they're gonna
think that I'm I'm lazy cuz of course
they're gonna judge me based on the fact
that I'm a woman instead of the fact
that like I would like just hang out and
said Judd okay with it sure or like
doing my and even in like feminist
circles I do find that women end up
cleaning more doing more of the
childcare and doing more of everything
and there I probably do fall over on the
spectrum like I'd probably do clean less
in group settings and give less of the
like female like the clean domestic
chores and other people do I don't do
the dishes as well I don't but if you
took across the entire population that
I'm probably average just
just that I bet I'm being compared with
it's like man and woman um so yeah my
videos on a longer day and I wanted to
talk about it now - but seeing this
thing that I'm struggling with thank you